http://www.thesunchronicle.com/site/privacy.html

Buy & Sell
Want to Advertise?
Attleboro, MA
(02703)
Today
Partly cloudy. High 52F. Winds SSW at 10 to 15 mph..
Tonight
Partly cloudy in the evening with more clouds for later at night. Low 36F. Winds SW at 5 to 10 mph.
Media Kit/Rate Card
Want to Advertise?
Subscribe
GENERAL INFORMATIONBy using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms of this privacy policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this privacy policy, please do not use the site.What personally identifiable information does the website collect from me?Information is collected in several ways. Some personal information is gathered through server log files. Personal information is also gathered when you enter a contest or promotion, subscribe, request vacation delivery stop, or when you place an online ad. During these instances, The Sun Chronicle asks for information such as your name, e-mail address, street address, zip code, phone number, subscriber status, and credit card number. We may also ask you for other information at other times.How is my information used?The Sun Chronicle uses information collected from server log files, such as IP addresses, to help diagnose problems with our services, to administer our Web site, and to report and gather aggregate information about site usage and user demographics. The aggregated data may be shared with advertisers or business partners and is not linked to personally identifiable information.Cookies are used to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web service and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are used to deliver targeted advertising based on your behavior or demographics and to track your number of entries in some of our promotions and contests. You can set your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do we will not be able to customize the Web site's features according to your preferences. Advertising networks that serve ads into our site, such as Real Media or DoubleClick, may also use their own cookies. For more information about Real Media's use of cookies, visit http://www.realmedia.com/privacy.html. For more information about DoubleClick's use of cookies, visit http://www.privacychoices.org.With whom is my information shared?Promotions and contests that run on the newspaper Web site may be sponsored by companies other than the newspaper Web site or may be co-sponsored by the newspaper Web site and another company. The newspaper may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to our Web site users. Some of these forums require registration. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Aggregate information compiled by the newspaper Web site may be shared with advertisers and business partners as well as used by the newspaper and its related companies.Linked SitesPlease be aware that the newspaper Web site's promotional partners, advertisers, sponsors, third-party Internet sites, and content providers accessible through The Sun Chronicle.com may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. The newspaper and Web site are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third party parties. Users should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing personally identifiable information through co-sponsored, affiliated or linked sites.Children's GuidelinesThe Newspaper in Education program is a free service the newspaper may offer for teachers which promotes the use of newspapers in the classroom. The information requested on these pages is used solely for participation in the particular activity, and is not stored or sold to third parties. If a question, comment, story, joke, idea or opinion is published, only the student's first name, grade and state/country appear on the site. Students are advised to consult with their parents before giving personal information online.Associated Press News RegistryThis Web site uses services provided by News Registry. News Registry collects content usage information and may use cookies in conjunction with this activity.Your continued readership of the Site means you accept the privacy policy of News Registry. Please refer to the News Registry privacy policy at http://www.apnewsregistry.com/privacycenter/servicepolicy.aspx for further information.Children's Privacy PolicyThe newspaper is committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. The newspaper does not ask children to disclose more personal information than is necessary for them to participate in a particular activity. We urge children to check with their parents before entering information on any website and we urge parents to discuss with their children restrictions regarding the online release of personal information to anyone they don't know.Information CollectedThe newspaper limits its collection of information from children to what is known as nonpersonally identifiable information (e.g. screen names, birthday, gender, city, state, zip code and country of residence). This information is collected so children can participate in activities (e.g. completing polls or online surveys, posting jokes, book reviews, movie reviews, toy reviews, video reviews, concert reviews, game reviews, artwork or questions/comments online, or playing online games) without giving unnecessary personal information. From time to time, however, we may request limited personally identifiable information (e.g. child's email address and/or parent's or guardian's email address), as explained below, in order to conduct online contests or sweepstakes or offer other online activities. The newspaper cannot and does not condition a child's participation in any of our online activities on the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. Information is collected actively, such as through registration forms, and passively, such as through cookies.Contest and SweepstakesThe newspaper occasionally offers contest and sweepstakes, which may be entered online. Children under 13 may not participate in any online contest offered by The Sun Chronicle.Use of InformationThe newspaper may disclose information maintained as required by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. The newspaper may also disclose such information in response to a specific law enforcement agency's request.CookiesThe newspaper uses a software technology called "cookies." Cookies are small files that we place in visitors' computer browsers to store their preferences. Cookies themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information. Although cookies could enable the newspaper to relate a visitor's use of this website to personal information that the visitor has provided, such as an email address, we do not use cookies for this purpose. We do use cookies to determine how many visitors we have and how often they visit various sections of our site. You can, of course, disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser.Parental AccessParents, please send a letter or postcard to our Privacy Coordinator at the mailing address provided below if you would like to do any of the following:Access personally identifiable information that The Sun Chronicle has collected online from your child,Correct factual errors in such information,Request to have this information deleted, orRequest that we no longer collect or maintain such information.Please include your e-mail address and telephone number where we can reach you. The Sun Chronicle takes steps to verify the identity of anyone requesting information about a child and to ensure that the person is in fact the child's parent or legal guardian.FeedbackComments? Questions? Suggestions? Send e-mail to news@thesunchronicle.com. You can also use our directory to e-mail our staff directly, or send a card or letter to:Privacy CoordinatorThe Sun Chronicle34 South Main StreetAttleboro, MA 02703OtherJ. Carter MarketingWe use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our Web site. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your on your browser.This company may use information (provided by this "cookie") in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by this company, please visit http://www.jcartermarketing.com/JCM_Privacy_Policy.pdf
© Copyright 2020 The Sun Chronicle, 34 South Main Street Attleboro, MA | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
